<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deepen Saha</title>
    <link>https://deepensaha.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Deepen Saha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:15:34 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://deepensaha.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://deepensaha.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:15:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deepensaha.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently the Tech Lead at GrayQuest Finance and possess over 5 years of expertise as a Full Stack Developer.
My forte primarily lies in building large scale automated systems. A penchant for technology is the result of my passion to solve problems by leveraging the same. I am particularly interested in automation and open source projects. In my leisure time, I read and absorb the latest updates about everything tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://deepensaha.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:35:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deepensaha.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://deepensaha.github.io/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:26:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deepensaha.github.io/work/</guid>
      <description>Vice President Of Engineering  GrayQuest Finance, Mumbai  June 2021 - Present   Leading a team of 12+ professionals to build fully Automated Financial Systems. Spearheading the architecture and development of platforms as well as services for Automated Financial Workflows and Loan Management Systems.  Instrumental in the upgrades and development of GrayQuest&#39;s Repayment and Reconciliation, Customer, Lender, Institute, Partner, and LMS Platforms. Boosted sales by 10x through automation and reducing customer flow frictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Logging — A Weapon for Debuggers</title>
      <link>https://deepensaha.github.io/updates/2020/09/django-logging-a-weapon-for-debuggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deepensaha.github.io/updates/2020/09/django-logging-a-weapon-for-debuggers/</guid>
      <description>Django logging configuration and usage for Beginners. In the simplest way printing out data into a file or console (terminal) making it easier for developers to trace back the source of errors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>